Ostap Klysa



ostapklysa@gmail.com



937373213



linkedin.com/in/ostap-klysa-425237108



https://github.com/BrunoUA96

Summary

Passionate developer offering 5+ years of experience, strong sense of web design and commitment to the user experience, including the accessibility.

Working on wide range of project types, from landing pages to large platforms.

Fast adaptation to new Technologies, Frameworks and Program Languages.

Comfortable with working with code written by others, and development from scratch.

Excellent communication skills and great collaborator.

- 5+ web development
- Experience in creating and improving web UI/UX
- 2 years in creating web applications in angular (version 7+)
- In my spare time I'm interested in React and Node JS

Experience

INF® Full-stack Developer

Info 2000

Jul 2021 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

- B2C platforms for Clients
- Transition of Desktop (Java) application to Web (Angular)
- Angular Material, RESTful API, HTML, CSS/SASS (Bootstrap), TypeScript, MySQL, PHP

Full-stack Developer

Freelance

Jan 2019 - Jun 2021 (2 years 6 months)

Main Projects:

Aircoach.site (Sports & Health platform for US market)

Borzoidesign.com (exclusive design objects and art gallery)

Out-emotion.pt (landing page for Electric bikes rental)

Driveyou.pt (Transfers and Private Tours)

- Design UI/UX
- Frontend using HTML, CSS/SASS (Bootstrap), JavaScript
- Razor ASP.NET
- Backend using OctoberCMS

Frontend Developer

JUNTA Digital Production

Mar 2017 - Nov 2019 (2 years 9 months)

- Responsible for HTML, CSS/SASS (Bootstrap), JavaScript
- Participation in Design creation
- Frontend integration using OctoberCMS

Main Projects: labrador.pt, edulog.pt, casadasciencias.org, hiseedtech.com, almbeer.com, etc

Education

Escola profissional Novos Horizontes

Informação Profissional, Gestão de Informatica 2011 - 2014

Skills

TypeScript • UI/UX • SASS • JavaScript • Angular • MySQL • PHP • REST APIs • Agile Methodologies • Bootstrap